DARRON GORDON

DETAILS

Johannesburg South Africa 066 258 8965

darronmgordon@gmail.com

• SKILLS •

Unity
HTML
CSS
C#
React
JavaScript
jQuery
Node.js
Express.js
MongoDB
MySQL
GitHub
SASS
Python

• LINKS •

Portfolio Site

Itch.lo

♥JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA <u></u>066 258 8965

Hardworking and self accountable. I have extensive experience in Unity, C#, mono and network Behaviour. I am skilled in Web-Development and Web3 blockchains. I have worked on Building automation controls and networks for studio's and pharmaceutical factories HVAC control's.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Development and game design

January 2020 - Present

Operations Manager at DarronAir, Johannesburg

January 2019 — January 2020

Technician at I.P.L Engineering, Johannesberg

January 2014 — January 2015

• Ammonia Refrigeration

Technical Manager at S.C.M.C Delta Controls, Johannesburg January

2007 — January 2019

- Delta BMS/BAC
- HVAC

Freelancer, Johannesburg

- Game-Jams / Hackathon
- Game-Development
- Web-Development
- App-Development EDUCATION

Education

PCEP, Python Institute N1,

Technisa, Johannesburg

Apprentiship, SCMC

Delta BAC/BMS Apprenticeship.

Skills

-Unity 2D & 3D

- 2D and 3D Game Design
- MonoBehaviour
- NetworkBehaviour(Fish-net, Mirror, UNet)
- Windows/ Web-GL(Html5) / Android Builds
- VFX(Particle system, VFX Graph, VFX Shader)
- Web3 Block-Chain integration
- New and old Input systems
- A-star Pathfinding
- Scriptable Objects

- Code design patterns (Finite state machine, singleton, Observer, Pooling ect..)
- Animations(keyframe, Rigging)

-Web & JS

- HTML
- CSS, SASS, SCSS (FlexBox, Bootstrap)
- React.JS
- React Native
- Canvas & iframe

-Design

- Photoshop / Krita
- Spine
- Blender
- Unity

-Noteworthy

- 1st Place MFG Web3 NEAR block-chain Game-Jam
- www.darrongordon.click